잠깐, 기다려, 너 보러 여기 오시진 않겠지?
Wait, wait, she's not gonna come here looking for you, is she?
괜찮아. 쉘든이랑 뇌파 측정하러 병원가셨어
Relax. She took Sheldon to the hospital to get a brain scan.
오.. 무슨일 있었니??
Oh, my God. What happened?
아무것도 아냐. 그냥 뇌파 보는걸 좋아하셔
Nothing. Mother likes looking at brains
그리고 쉘든은 자기 뇌파 검사하는걸 좋아하고
and Sheldon likes getting his brain scanned.
ㅎㄷㄷ 아주 웃긴 커플이네
Geez, what a fun couple.
하루 반동안만 여기 계실거야
She's only been here a day and a half
그리고 난 알콜중독을 새 직업상 진로로 삼을지 생각중이야
and I'm seriously considering alcoholism
어제 5분 정도 네 어머니와 이야기 했었는데
Hey, I talked to her for five minutes yesterday
그때부터 지금까지 난 계속 반쯤 취해있었어
and I've been half bombed ever since.
우리는 네 머리속에 그녀가 들어가게 하면 안되
You can't let her get into your head.